pay-box.in 2017-08-07

# Online free recharge,Free recharge offer,Free recharge tricks,Free recharge offers,Online free recharge,Free online recharge,Free recharge online,Free recharge,Free recharge offers,Free talktime - paybox.

PayBox is committed to protect the privacy of the users who access its platform (the Platform). This privacy policy statement (the Privacy Policy) generally explains the types of information PayBox gathers and what PayBox does with it. By using or visiting the Platform, you agree to (i) the terms and policies described in this Privacy Policy; and (ii) to the collection of information described in this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy addresses the PayBox privacy and data protection practices and also outlines PayBox’s business, how PayBox works, and how PayBox’s technology interacts with personal information from three sources: 

Non-registered visitors to www.Pay-box.in (Visitors). 

Registered members of the Platform (Member(s)). 

Web users who click on offers, banners or any other PayBox offering (End Users). 

**1.** Collecting Personally Identifiable Information 

PayBox collects from Members Personally Identifiable Information (as defined below). You acknowledge such collection of information is done on a voluntary basis to enable PayBox to provide you efficient access to features, functions, promotions, products and services. 

Personally Identifiable Information means any information given by a Member to PayBox or obtained through the use of the Platform which might reasonably be used to specifically identify you and may include, among other, your name, title, location, phone number, address or email. 

**2.** Non-Personal Information 

PayBox automatically collects from Members non-personal information such as IP addresses, the content and pages that you access on the Platform, and the dates and times that you visit the Platform, paths taken, and time spent on sites and pages during your access and use of the Platform. PayBox automatically collects from Visitors non-personal information such as IP addresses and other web information. PayBox automatically collects from End Users non-personal information such as IP addresses, a unique user ID, sites that s/he arrived from, impressions, clicks and the completion of offers/tasks.Impressions, clicks and the completion of offers/tasks are collected on an aggregated demographic base (per age, gender and country). Non-Personal Information means any information collected by PayBox under sections 2(i) through 2(iii).Non-Personal Information is used, amongst others, to help diagnose problems with PayBox’s server, to identify ways of making the Platform better, for security and monitoring purposes and to present the user with the most relevant offers and/or banners for him. 

**3.** Use of Digital Identifiers 

PayBox automatically uses Digital Identifiers (as defined below), amongst others, for tracking activities, identification, security and/or the user characteristics. No Personally Identifiable Information is collected by use of Digital Identifier. PayBox uses the information collected through Digital Identifiers, amongst others, to analyze trends, administer the Platform, track movements on the Platform and gather aggregate demographic information about visitors so that PayBox can continually improve the Platform. This Privacy Policy covers the use of Digital Identifiers by PayBox and does not cover the use of Digital Identifiers by any third party (such as advertisers) who may be promoted through the Platform (Digital Identifiers will be used for all users of the Platform). 

Cookies means information that a website puts on your hard disk so that it can remember something about you at a later time (more technically, it is information for future use that is stored by the server on the client side of a client/server communication). 

Web Beacons means a transparent GIF image that enables PayBox to count page views and to retrieve information from the Cookies PayBox saved on your computer. 

Digital Identifier means Cookies or Web Beacons. 

**4.** Security 

PayBox employs industry standard security measures to ensure the security of data it collects. Any data that is stored on PayBox’s servers is treated as proprietary and confidential. PayBox maintains an internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of your data. 

While PayBox has taken measures to protect information it collected, please know that (i) no computer system is immune from intrusion; and (ii) information transmitted to the Platform may need to pass through many systems in order to process such information. Therefore, PayBox cannot guarantee the absolute security or confidentiality of information transmitted to the Platform and you hereby acknowledge and assume the risks relating to any such communication. 

**5.** Information Sharing 

PayBox may use the collected Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personal Information (together Information) for any legally permissible purpose in its sole discretion, including, but not limited to, the following: 

Sharing Information with affiliated companies. This Privacy Policy does not apply to affiliated companies and their collection, use and sharing of information. 

Sharing Information with various third party vendors that are not part of PayBox (or its affiliates). Using third party service providers to enhance the Platform with additional elements of PayBox’s services. 

**6.** Third Party Links 

The Platform may offer links to other websites. Other websites have their own terms of use and privacy and security policies. If you choose to visit one of these websites, you should review the policies that govern that particular website. 

**7.** Permitted Disclosures 

Other than as described in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise specifically communicated to you by PayBox, PayBox will not provide Information to any third parties, except where law, court order, or governmental authority requires or based upon the good faith belief that disclosure is necessary including, without limitation, to protect the rights of PayBox when we have reason to believe that disclosing the Information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with PayBox’s rights or causing harm to third parties. 

**8.** Revision 

PayBox may alter, update or otherwise change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such changes will be posted on this page. You should periodically check this Privacy Policy to review the current terms and guidelines. Your continued use of the Platform following the posting of such changes will indicate your full acceptance of those changes. 

**9.** PayBox’s Commitment to Children’s Privacy 

IF YOU ARE UNDER 18 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE PLATFORM AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. 

PayBox does not knowingly collect or maintain Personally Identifiable Information from persons under 18 years-of-age. If PayBox learns that Personally Identifiable Information of persons less than 18-years-of-age has been collected on or through the Platform, then PayBox will take reasonable steps to delete this information. 

If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 18 who uses the Platform, then please contact PayBox at support@pay-box.in to have that child’s Information deleted. 

**10.** Updating Your Personal Information 

Members can access and correct their Information and privacy preferences by accessing their "Account details" page in the "My Account" menu in the Platform, or by sending an e-mail to support@pay-box.in. To the extent permissible under the applicable law, Members may occasionally receive e-mail messages from PayBox 

**11.** Contact Us 

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please send an e-mail to support@pay-box.in. If you believe that PayBox has not complied with this Privacy Policy with respect to your Information or you have other related inquiries or concerns, you may write to PayBox at the following address or e-mail: support@pay-box.in. 

YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS WELL AS, IF APPLICABLE, THE GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS BETWEEN YOU AND PAYBOX AND THE PLATFORM (INCLUDING LIMITATIONS ON DAMAGES).
